OKAY, PICK A CARD.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW... MEMORIZE IT.
YOU GOT IT?
OH, YES.
OKAY. IS THAT YOUR CARD?
YES.
( chuckling ):
YEAH, IT IS.
HEY, GUYS.
HI, THERE!
Ben: HI!
GUESS WHAT?
BEN IS GOING TO BE
IN A TV COMMERCIAL.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WELL... IT'S NOT FOR SURE
BUT, UH, WE MET THIS GUY
IN THE PARK
WHO THOUGHT BEN
WAS REALLY CUTE, YOU KNOW...
WHICH HE IS.
UM, ANYWHO, HE, UH,
HE GAVE US HIS CARD
AND TOLD US
TO BRING HIM DOWN
FOR THIS COMMERCIAL
HE'S AUDITIONING.
WHOA. THIS GUY'S, LIKE
THE BIGGEST COMMERCIAL-CASTING
DIRECTOR IN TOWN!
BEN TAKES ONE LOUSY WALK
IN THE PARK
AND GETS AN AUDITION?!
I MEAN, "WAY TO GO, BEN!"
MAN, I'VE BEEN IN THAT PARK
A MILLION TIMES.
NO ONE'S EVER OFFERED ME
AN AUDITION.
I KNOW. IT'S CRAZY--
WE WERE JUST PUSHING
BEN ON THE SWINGS...
I'M ALWAYS ON THE SWINGS!
( whining ):
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
THAT.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OKAY, GOT TO GO. WISH ME LUCK.
HEY, RACH, NOW THAT YOU'RE
WORKING AT RALPH LAUREN
CAN YOU BRING ME BACK
SOME OF THOSE POLO SHIRTS?
UH, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'D FEEL COMFORTABLE
STEALING ON MY VERY FIRST DAY.
UNWILLING TO STEAL FROM WORK...
INTERESTING.
BESIDES, IF
ANYBODY'S GOING
TO GET FREE STUFF
IT'S GOING TO BE ME.
OKAY, GUYS,
WAY TO WISH ME LUCK.
GOOD LUCK.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
BYE.
OKAY, LET'S DISCUSS
RACHEL'S BIRTHDAY.
I SAY WE THROW HER
A SURPRISE PARTY THIS WEEKEND.
WHOA, BUT HER BIRTHDAY'S
NOT FOR, LIKE, ANOTHER MONTH.
OKAY, BUT IF WE THROW HER
A PARTY ON HER BIRTHDAY
THEN IT'S NOT A SURPRISE.
I THINK THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE CAN HAVE A DINNER PARTY
AND JUST INVITE
HER CLOSE FRIENDS.
ROSS! WE'RE HAVING
A SURPRISE PARTY FOR RACHEL!
Ross:
OKAY!
DONE.
OKAY, GREAT, SO DO YOU WANT
TO DO IT TOGETHER?
I WOULD LOVE
TO DO IT TOGETHER.
OOH!
( fiendish laughter )
THEY'RE GOING TO DO IT
TOGETHER.
DUDE, THAT'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
OH, SO I GOT
TO SHUT IT DOWN NOW?
ALL RIGHT. I
GOT TO TAKE OFF.
I'M PICKING UP BEN
AND THEN WE'RE OFF
TO THE BIG AUDITION.
I BET IT'S GOING
TO BE WEIRD SEEING SOME ACTOR
PRETENDING TO
BE BEN'S DAD.
YEAH.
WEIRDER THAN SEEING
HIS TWO MOMS MAKE OUT?
WHOA, WHOA, "DAD"?
THERE'S A DAD IN THE COMMERCIAL?
YEAH. THE DAD AND BEN EAT SOUP
AND PRETEND TO ENJOY IT.
MAYBE I'LL GO DOWN WITH YOU
AND SEE IF I CAN GET
AN AUDITION AS THE DAD.
WHO BETTER THAN TO PLAY
BEN'S FATHER THAN HIS GODFATHER?
YOU'RE NOT HIS GODFATHER.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
OF COURSE I AM.
( sighing )
OKAY, LET'S GO,
GODFATHER.
ALL RIGHT! WHOA.
HEY! I'M IN.
THEY'RE GOING TO
LET ME AUDITION.
REALLY? THAT'S GREAT.
IT TURNS OUT ONE OF
THE CASTING LADIES
HAS ACTUALLY
SEEN ME IN A PLAY
SO I STEERED
CLEAR OF HER.
Carol:
HEY, THAT KID
LOOKS FAMILIAR.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
HE'S DONE TONS
OF COMMERCIALS.
I'VE SEEN HIM IN, LIKE,
SUGAR SMACKS, PLAYSTATION
AND THAT ONE FOR
THE PHONE COMPANY.
IN FACT, HE WAS
SO GOOD IN THAT ONE
HE ACTUALLY CONVINCED ME
TO SWITCH PHONE COMPANIES.
( chuckling ):
CHANDLER WAS MAD...
YEAH, WELL, HE'S NOT GOING
TO GET THIS ONE, ALL RIGHT?
BEN IS WAY CUTER
THAN THAT KID.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HIM--
LOOK AT YOU!
( speaking gibberish )
( sniffling )
( chuckling ):
THAT'S... GREAT.
LISTEN, WOULDN'T IT
BE GREAT, THOUGH
IF I GOT TO PLAY
BEN'S DAD?
JOEY, YOU LOOK
NOTHING LIKE BEN.
I LOOK MORE LIKE
HIM THAN YOU DO.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY DON'T
KNOW YOU WELL ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO DO THAT.
SO, IT'S DOWN
TO THESE TWO.
NANCY, I KNOW
YOU LIKE THIS ONE,
AND I THINK I AGREE.
RACHEL, WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
WELL, UM, I MEAN,
THAT ONE IS PRETTY
BUT, OH, I JUST...
I JUST LOVE THIS FABRIC.
SORRY.
OH, DON'T BE SORRY.
IT'S PART OF YOUR JOB
TO GIVE YOUR OPINIONS
AND THEN I TAKE CREDIT
FOR THEM. I'M KIDDING.
SHE IS KIDDING...
BUT DON'T EVER DISAGREE
WITH HER AGAIN.
OKAY, NOW I'M KIDDING.
( nervous laugh ):
OH, WHAT A FUN OFFICE.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE,
BUT I DO KNOW I NEED A CIGARETTE
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE TAKE A BREAK, WE GO OUTSIDE
AND WE'LL FIGURE THIS THING OUT
WHEN WE COME BACK?
RACHEL?
YEAH?
YOU SMOKE?
OH, NO. MY DAD'S A DOCTOR
AND HE WOULD ALWAYS TELL ME
JUST HORROR STORIES...
ABOUT, UH, GHOSTS
AND GOBLINS...
WHO... TOTALLY SUPPORTED
THE PRINCESS'S RIGHT TO SMOKE.
AND THEN THEY CAME BACK
FROM SMOKING
AND THEY HAD MADE ALL
OF THE DECISIONS WITHOUT ME.
THAT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE I'M BEING PUNISHED
FOR NOT HAVING THIS DISGUSTING,
POISONOUS HABIT.
YEAH, IT IS THE BEST.
I MEAN, WHAT IF THIS KEEPS
HAPPENING, YOU KNOW?
THEY'LL-THEY'LL
BE OUTSIDE SMOKING
MAKING ALL THE DECISIONS,
AND I'LL JUST BE UP IN MY OFFICE
BREATHING IN
MY STUPID CLEAN AIR, YOU KNOW?
AND THEN WHEN THE DAY COMES WHEN
KIM WANTS TO PROMOTE ONE OF US
WHO DO YOU THINK
SHE'S GOING TO PICK--
ME OR SMOKEY SMOKERSON?
RACHEL, YOU CAN GO DOWN THERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SMOKE.
JUST SAY YOU WANT TO
GET SOME... FRESH AIR.
YEAH, I COULD DO THAT.
YEAH, OR YOU COULD JUST DO
THE EASY THING AND SMOKE.
( knocking )
HEY.
RACH, DO YOU WANT
TO GO GET COFFEE?
OH, I WOULD LOVE TO.
OH, GOOD!
I'LL GO TOO, BABE.
OH, GOOD.
YAY.
YAH.
OH, I CHANGED MY MIND.
OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE PARTY.
I HAVE SO MANY IDEAS.
ME, TOO!
OH!
YEAH!
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S A LITTLE
SKETCH OF THE CAKE.
UH-HUH.
SEE?
UM, SOME SAMPLE MENUS, UM...
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
WE'D START OUT
WITH TUSCAN-STYLE
FINGER FOOD, OKAY?
AND FOR MUSIC, HERE'S
AN ALPHABETIZED LIST
OF ALL OF MY CDs.
I'VE HIGHLIGHTED THE ONES
THAT'LL GO REALLY
GOOD WITH THE FOOD.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE INTIMATE DINNER PARTY?
YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT
DOING THAT, OKAY?
WOW. ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE YOU TOOK CARE
OF EVERYTHING.
THANKS A LOT,
CO-HOST.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DIDN'T TAKE CARE
OF EVERYTHING.
THERE'S PLENTY OF THINGS
FOR YOU TO DO.
UH-HUH. LIKE WHAT?
CUPS!
CUPS? YOU'RE
GIVING ME CUPS?
AND ICE.
CUPS AND ICE?
OH, I GET TO BE IN
CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
OKAY, I WILL BE IN
CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE.
WAIT A MINUTE,
I CAN GET ICE
AT THE RESTAURANT.
I GOT IT! MINE!
Monica:
HEY.
HI.
HOW'D THE AUDITION GO?
NOT SO GOOD.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU DOING JOEY'S...
"THE AUDITION DIDN'T
GO SO WELL...
YEAH, IT DID!"
YEAH, I AM!
( screaming )
YEAH, BEN GOT
A SECOND AUDITION!
GREAT!
YEAH, I HAD TO TEACH
ROSS MY BIT
'CAUSE I ACTUALLY DIDN'T
GET A CALLBACK.
YOU GOT A CALLBACK,
TOO, DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH, I DID!
HEY, RACHEL, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING OUT HERE?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT GOT
KIND OF LONELY UP THERE
SO I JUST THOUGHT
I WOULD COME OUT HERE AND...
GET SOME FRESH AIR.
( coughing )
NANCY AND I WERE
TALKING ABOUT THE
FALL COLLECTION.
OH, GREAT.
SO, ANYWAY...
( coughing )
HONEY, I'M SORRY.
WE'RE SMOKING
ALL OVER YOU.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
WE'LL MOVE. YOU
STAY RIGHT HERE.
Nancy:
SO I WAS
THINKING...
THANKS.
OH, THAT'S
GREAT.
YOU ARE THE BEST.
EXCUSE ME, CAN I
BUM ONE OF THOSE?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY...
( both laughing )
OKAY, OKAY, WHAT'S
SO FUNNY OVER HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU
DIDN'T SMOKE.
OH, YOU KNOW, I-I THOUGHT
YOU GUYS MEANT
MARIJUANA CIGARETTES, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, DOOBIES?
ACTUALLY, I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"WOW, THOSE GUYS ARE CRAZY!"
BUT, NO, ACTUALLY,
I SMOKE THE REGULAR ONES
ALL... ALL THE TIME.
WE GET HIGH.
( stammering ):
ME, TOO.
I'M KIDDING.
OH!
( weakly ):
ME, TOO.
OH, GOD, THIS IS
SO NERVE-RACKING.
HOW-HOW DO YOU DO THIS?
WELL, FORTUNATELY, I DON'T
GET MANY CALLBACKS, SO...
IS IT A GOOD SIGN
THAT THEY ASKED US
TO HANG AROUND
AFTER THE AUDITION?
WHO KNOWS?
OKAY, UH, WE HAVE NARROWED IT
DOWN TO RAYMOND, BEN
KYLE AND JOEY.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YES! I KNEW IT!
( sighing ):
BYE-BYE...
SO LONG...
LATER.
ROSS, THIS IS GREAT.
I MIGHT ACTUALLY GET
TO PLAY BEN'S DAD.
YEAH!
ACTUALLY, THAT
CAN'T HAPPEN.
BECAUSE YOU ALL HAVE
SUCH DIFFERENT LOOKS
WE'RE PUTTING YOU
WITH RAYMOND
AND KYLE WITH BEN.
SO IT'LL EITHER BE
YOU TWO OR YOU TWO.
OH, MAN...
THIS IS GOING TO BE
KIND OF WEIRD.
YEAH, IT IS..
YEAH. IT'S GOING
TO BE WEIRD.
NO, WE'RE-WE'RE,
LIKE, BEST FRIENDS.
THAT'S-THAT'S
WHY IT'S WEIRD.
OH, OH.
I-I THOUGHT WE WERE
JUST... TALKING.
HEY.
IS IT OKAY IF I LEAVE
THIS STUFF HERE
TILL RACHEL'S
BIRTHDAY PARTY?
SURE. WHAT'S
IN THEM?
UM, CUPS.
OH, GOOD, BECAUSE WE GOT RACHEL
800 GALLONS OF WATER.
SERIOUSLY, THAT'S
A LOT OF CUPS.
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S 'CAUSE
I'M IN CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE
AND MONICA IS GOING
TO RUE THE DAY
THAT SHE PUT ME IN CHARGE
OF CUPS AND ICE.
YOU KNOW, I RUED THE DAY ONCE.
DIDN'T GET
A WHOLE LOT ELSE DONE.
OKAY, TIME TO BRING UP
THE REST OF THE CUPS.
OH, HEY, JOEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
Ross:
HEY.
ROSS, GOOD.
I'M, UH, GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
OH? WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS WHOLE COMMERCIAL THING.
YOU KNOW,
ME GOING UP AGAINST BEN
THE TWO OF US COMPETING, AND...
WELL, THAT CAN'T LEAD
TO ANYTHING GOOD
SO... I THINK
I'M JUST GOING TO STEP ASIDE.
I'M GOING TO TELL THEM
THAT I WON'T AUDITION.
WOW, UH...
JOEY, THAT'S... THAT'S GREAT.
THANKS, MAN.
THAT'S IT?
YOU-YOU'RE GOING
TO LET ME DO THIS?
THIS IS MY CAREER
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE.
BUT... BUT YOU JUST...
I JUST SAID THAT SO YOU WOULDN'T
LET BEN DO IT.
LOOK, ROSS, IF ANYONE SHOULD
STEP ASIDE, IT SHOULD BE BEN.
WHAT?
CHANDLER, TELL HIM.
WELL, LET ME... LET
ME GET THE DOOR FIRST.
OH, HI, NO ONE.
WHY SHOULD BEN
STEP ASIDE?
IT WAS HIS AUDITION
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YOU JUST TAGGED ALONG.
YOU'RE LIKE THE...
THE TAG-ALONG DAD.
AT LEAST I CARE
ABOUT HIS FEELINGS.
WH-WH-WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD
THIS WILL BE ON HIM
WHEN HE DOESN'T GET IT?
AND WHY WOULDN'T HE GET IT?
OH, COME ON.
HAVE YOU SEEN
WHAT MY KID CAN DO?
HUH?
I MEAN, HE DIALS PHONES
HE-HE EATS TORTILLA CHIPS.
HE-HE PLAYS SOCCER WITH
THE CARTOON TIGER.
ARE YOU SAYING YOUR KID
EATS SOUP BETTER THAN MY KID?
YOU JUST GIVE HIM
A SPOON, BABY.
OH, YEAH? I GUESS WE'LL SEE.
YEAH
BECAUSE THIS COMMERCIAL
BELONGS TO ME AND MITCH.
YOUR KID'S NAME IS RAYMOND.
YEAH, SO'S YOURS!
HOW DID WORK GO?
OH, IT WAS GREAT.
I WENT DOWN THERE JUST
LIKE YOU SAID, YOU KNOW,
AND WE TALKED BUSINESS
AND KIM TOTALLY TOOK
MY OPINIONS.
YOU STINK.
THANKS.
NO, I'M-I'M SERIOUS.
WELL, THAT-THAT'S JUST
'CAUSE I WENT DOWN THERE
AND THEY WERE ALL SMOKING.
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE
SMELL OF SUCCESS.
OKAY, BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING DIFFERENT, THOUGH.
OH, MY GOD. YOU SMOKED.
( gasping )
I DID NOT.
YES, YOU DID. YOU LOOK HAPPY
AND SICK-- YOU SMOKED!
ALL RIGHT, FINE, BUT I HAD TO.
I HAD TO DO IT FOR MY CAREER.
I WISH I HAD TO SMOKE
FOR MY CAREER.
BUT IT'S SO GROSS.
DON'T... NO, WELL, NO,
IT'S NOT THAT BAD, YOU KNOW.
IT'S... I MEAN, YEAH,
MY TONGUE FEELS A LITTLE FUZZY
AND MY FINGERS SORT OF SMELL.
I ACTUALLY FEEL
LIKE I COULD THROW UP.
OKAY, BUT YOU GOT
TO PUSH PAST THIS, OKAY?
BECAUSE IT'S ABOUT
TO GET SO GOOD.
CHANDLER.
OH, I GOT TO TELL YOU,
YOU SMELL SO SMOKY
I GOT... I-I GOT TO GET UP.
WHAT?
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I THINK YOU SMELL GREAT.
SO, WE'RE DECIDED--
NO ON PLAID, YES ON PINK.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M SO ON-BOARD.
MM-HMM.
RACHEL, DIDN'T YOU
JUST LIGHT THAT?
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST REALLY, REALLY
TRYING TO CUT BACK, YOU KNOW.
GOOD LUCK, RACH.
I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN
THINKING ABOUT
QUITTING LATELY.
OH, WELL, SURE--
EVERY SUNDAY NIGHT
I TELL MYSELF I'M QUITTING.
EVERY MONDAY MORNING,
IT'S LIKE...
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
WELL, LET'S JUST QUIT.
WE'LL JUST QUIT.
LET'S ALL QUIT.
IT DOES SOUND APPEALING.
I NEVER COULD DO IT.
OH, BUT YOU COULD.
YOU CAN. ABSOLUTELY.
WE CAN HELP
EACH OTHER OUT.
YOU KNOW, WE COULD GET--
WHAT? WHAT?-- THOSE PATCHES.
WE COULD BE LIKE
THE PATCH SISTERS.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WE REALLY SHOULD QUIT.
OKAY, LET'S QUIT.
YES. GREAT.
GIVE ME THOSE CIGS.
COME ON, GIVE IT. GIVE IT.
OUT, DONE. QUIT. WHOO!
MY LATE HUSBAND
GAVE ME THAT LIGHTER.
SHE'S FUNNY.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
OKAY, THEN. OKAY.
MMM... SOUP.
MMM, SOUP.
JOEY, ROSS IS GOING
TO BE HERE ANY SECOND.
WOULD YOU MIND WATCHING
BEN FOR ME WHILE I USE
THE LADIES ROOM?
OH, YEAH. NO PROBLEM.
MMM, SOUP.
HI, BEN.
SO YOU WANT TO BE
AN ACTOR, HUH?
WELL, I GOT TO TELL
YOU, IT'S NO PICNIC.
THERE'S TONS OF REJECTION.
NO STABILITY.
I MEAN, ONE DAY YOU'RE
DR. DRAKE RAMORAY.
THE NEXT DAY,
YOU'RE EATING KETCHUP
RIGHT OUT OF THE BOTTLE.
JOEY.
ROSS.
BEN.
I MEAN, BEN, BEN.
OKAY.
RAYMOND, JOEY,
YOU'RE UP.
HEY.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, LET'S...
LET'S TRY ONE.
WHENEVER YOU GUYS ARE READY.
UH-OH.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
WELL, THIS IS NOODLE SOUP
AND I'VE BEEN
WORKING WITH TOMATO.
SO... BUT THAT'S OKAY.
NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM.
MMM, NOODLE SOUP.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THAT-THAT'S FINE
BUT THE LINE IS, "MMM, SOUP."
OH. WHAT DID I SAY?
"MMM, NOODLE SOUP."
HOW'S THAT DIFFERENT?
OH! I SEE, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S TRY ONE.
MMM, NOODLE SOUP.
OKAY.
LET'S... TRY IT AGAIN.
MMM, SOUP.
I MEAN NOODLE SOUP.
I MEAN SOUP.
COME ON!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE NEED TO MOVE ON.
NO, I COULD DO IT ONE MORE TIME.
SEE, LOOK.
MMM, NOODLE SOUP.
DAMN IT!
HEY. HEY!
UH-OH. BUSTED.
WELL, COME ON, YOU GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT WE WERE
THE PATCH SISTERS.
YEAH. THAT
DIDN'T WORK OUT.
RACHEL, WE TRIED TO QUIT,
BUT IT WAS TOO HARD.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU STARTED SMOKING AGAIN
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST TOLD ME.
COME ON. GIVE ME ONE OF THOSE.
WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
NO, NO. YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
DON'T YOU GIVE UP.
THAT'S WHY WE
DIDN'T TELL YOU
AND WE ARE NOT
GOING TO DRAG
YOU DOWN WITH US.
WAIT. NO, NO,
NO. DRAG ME DOWN.
DRAG-DRAG ME DOWN.
FORGET IT, RACHEL.
WE'RE BOTH SO PROUD
OF HOW WELL YOU'RE DOING.
I'M NOT GOING
TO LET YOU BLOW IT.
IN FACT, IF I CATCH YOU
WITH A CIGARETTE, YOU'RE FIRED.
GO ON. I DON'T WANT YOU
BREATHING THIS STUFF. GO ON.
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU'LL COME WITH ME
ON THE PARIS TRIP?
OH, MAN!
Chandler:
HEY.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
UM, CUP HAT, CUP BANNER,
CUP CHANDELIER
AND THE THING THAT
STARTED IT ALL--
THE CUP.
GREAT JOB
WITH THE CUPS, PHEEBS.
( giggling )
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GO OUT WITH HER?
AND DID YOU
NOTICE THE ICE?
LOOK, WE HAVE IT ALL--
WE HAVE CRUSHED,
CUBED AND DRY.
WATCH.
AHH... MYSTICAL.
OH, YES.
CHANDLER...
IF IT WEREN'T...
NO ONE'S EATING
MY TUSCAN FINGER FOOD
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL FILLING UP
ON PHOEBE'S SNO-CONES.
THERE ARE SNO-CONES?
SNO-CONES? YECH!
YOU KNOW, GO, GO.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
Phoebe:
OH, LOOK, LOOK!
All:
SURPRISE!
WHAT?!
MY BIRTHDAY
IS NOT FOR ANOTHER MONTH.
THAT'S THE SURPRISE.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU GUYS,
THIS IS SO GREAT.
IT'S SO UNEXPECTED.
I MEAN, CHANDLER'S BIRTHDAY'S
EVEN BEFORE MINE.
( weakly ):
SURPRISE.
WOW! THIS IS SO GREAT.
LOOK AT ALL THESE... CUPS.
THIS IS SO WEIRD.
I WAS IN CHARGE OF CUPS.
OH, OKAY. NOT SO WEIRD.
HEY.
LISTEN, MAN, UH... I'M SORRY
THE AUDITION DIDN'T GO WELL.
( snorts ):
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, REALLY, I AM, JOEY.
I FEEL BAD.
YEAH, WELL,
LOOK, ROSS...
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO, OKAY?
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT I SUCK.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF ACTOR
CAN'T EVEN SAY,
"MMM! NOODLE SOUP"?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE...
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T MESS UP
YOUR AUDITION
BECAUSE YOU SUCK.
MAYBE YOU MESSED UP
BECAUSE YOU CARE MORE
ABOUT YOUR GODSON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THINK
SUBCONSCIOUSLY...
WHOA-WHOA. YOU LOST ME.
I THINK ON SOME LEVEL
YOU-YOU SABOTAGED
YOUR OWN AUDITION
SO BEN WOULD GET THE PART.
WELL, YOUR WAY SOUNDS
A LOT BETTER THAN MINE.
YEAH. YEAH. IT'S NOT THAT
I'M A BAD ACTOR...
NO.
NO, IT'S JUST THAT, UH,
I CARE SO DAMN MUCH
ABOUT LITTLE BEN
THAT, UH, IT WAS MORE
IMPORTANT FOR ME TO
SEE HIM SUCCEED.
THERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
THANK YOU.
SO, DID HE GET IT?
NO.
AH, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
IS RACHEL HERE?
I'M MEETING HER
FOR LUNCH.
SHE DOESN'T COME DOWN HERE
ANYMORE.
YOU CAN FIND HER UP ON TEN.
OKAY, GREAT.
I'LL CATCH YOU GUYS LATER.